[
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_v2",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 40,
  "Task": "0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_v2_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "9206_Guardian",
  "AchievementId": "02_Quest_Armor_12_v2",
  "RequiredLevel": 40,
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_v2_Success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_title",
  "Description": "0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_description",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_v2",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 40,
  "Task": "1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_v2_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "9208_Shaman",
  "AchievementId": "13_Quest_Armor_11_v2",
  "RequiredLevel": 40,
  "SuccessGameEventId": "1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_v2_Success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_Title",
  "Description": "1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_Description",
  "PlayerPrompt": "1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_Complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_v2",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 40,
  "Task": "1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_v2_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "9207_Rogue",
  "AchievementId": "10_Quest_Armor_14_v2",
  "RequiredLevel": 40,
  "SuccessGameEventId": "1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_v2_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_objective_title",
  "Description": "1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_complete_available_response"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_lvl40_Weapon_v2",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_lvl40_Weapon_v2_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "9201_Cleric",
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_HopeManifest_00_v2",
  "RequiredLevel": 40,
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_lvl40_Weapon_v2_Success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_title",
  "Description": "0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_description",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_v2",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_v2_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "9202_Hunter",
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_TheHuntress_00_v2",
  "RequiredLevel": 40,
  "SuccessGameEventId": "1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_v2_Success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_Title",
  "Description": "1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_Description",
  "PlayerPrompt": "1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_Complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_v2",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_v2_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "9203_FirePriest",
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_FalmeasWrath_00_v2",
  "RequiredLevel": 40,
  "SuccessGameEventId": "1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_v2_Success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_Title",
  "Description": "1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_Description",
  "PlayerPrompt": "1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_Complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0204_0104_Executioner_lvl40_Weapon_v2",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "0204_0104_Executioner_lvl40_Weapon_v2_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "9204_Executioner",
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Executioner_00_v2",
  "RequiredLevel": 40,
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0204_0104_Executioner_lvl40_Weapon_v2_Success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0204_0104_Executioner_title",
  "Description": "0204_0104_Executioner_description",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0204_0104_Executioner_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0204_0104_Executioner_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0204_0104_Executioner_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0204_0104_Executioner_complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_v2",
  "Type": "EpicEquipment",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_v2_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "9205_Blademaster",
  "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_KeenTemper_00_v2",
  "RequiredLevel": 40,
  "SuccessGameEventId": "1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_v2_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "1hRShield_KeenTemperShieldT4",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_objective_title",
  "Description": "1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_complete_available_response"
 }
]